http://www.fashionista.com/page/privacy-policy

NewsBusinessStyleBeautyShoppingCareersNYC Job ListingsLA Job ListingsFashion WeekEditors' PicksEventsMeet the EditorsAboutContactAdvertiseJob ListingsEventsPrivacyTerms of ServicePlatform PrivacyPrivacy SettingsNewsBusinessStyleBeautyShoppingCareersFashion WeekEditors' PicksEvents
Privacy PolicyLast modified: February 14, 2013INTRODUCTIONFashionista, part of Breaking Media, Inc. (“We”) respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.This policy (together with our terms of use www.fashionista.com/terms-of-use and any other documents referred to in it) describes the personal information that we collect from you, or that you provide on this website www.fashionista.com (our “Website”) and how that information may be used or disclosed by us. The privacy policy of SAY Media, our exclusive advertising sales representative, may be found at http://www.saymedia.com/privacy-policy.This policy does not apply to information we collect through any other means, or to information collected on any other Company, affiliate, or third-party site, or by any third-party application that may link to or be accessible from the Website.Please read the following carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your personal information and how we will treat it. By using or accessing our Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time and your continued use of the Website is deemed to be acceptance of such changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 13Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, please do not register on the Website, make any purchases through the Website or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at services@breakingmedia.com or write to us at Breaking Media, Inc., a Delaware corporation located at 611 Broadway, Suite 907D, New York, New York 10012, Attn: Services.INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOUWe collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including:
Information you provide to us.
Information we collect as you navigate through the site, including usage details, IP addresses, and cookies and web beacons.
Information we receive from third parties, for example, our business partners.
INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE TO USWe may collect and use the following information that you provide to us:
Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Website, subscribing to our service, posting material or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you enter a contest or promotion sponsored by us, and when you report a problem with our Website.
Records and copies of your correspondence (including e-mail addresses and text messages), if you contact us.
Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.
Details of transactions you carry out through our Website and of the fulfillment of your orders. You may be required to provide financial information before placing an order through our Website.
USAGE DETAILS, IP ADDRESSES, COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS
Usage Details and IP Addresses. As you navigate through the Website, we may also collect details of your visits to our Website, including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, logs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access, as well as information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users’ equipment, browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.
Cookies. For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using cookies. A cookie is a small file stored on the hard drive of your computer. Use of cookies help us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service by enabling us to:
•Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
•Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.
•Speed up your searches.
•Recognize you when you return to our Website.
You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.
Web Beacons. Pages of the Website may contain electronic images known as web beacons (also referred to as single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company to count users who have visited those pages and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity). Web beacons are not used to access your personal information on the Website and are only used to compile aggregated statistics concerning use of the Website.
Third-Party Advertiser Use of Cookies and Web Beacons. Some advertisements on the Website are served by third-party advertising companies. Please note that our advertisers may also use cookies (alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies) to collect information about our users. We do not have control over third-party advertisers’ cookies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement, you should contact the responsible advertiser directly or contact SAY Media, our exclusive advertising sales representative, whose privacy policy may be found at http://www.saymedia.com/privacy-policy.php. We do not collect personally identifiable information automatically, but we may tie this information to your previously submitted personally identifiable information.
•To present our Website and its contents in a suitable and effective manner for you and for your computer.
•To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.
•To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.
•To notify you about changes to our service.
•To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.
•Our subsidiaries and affiliates.
•Contractors and service providers we use to support our business.
•SAY Media, our exclusive advertising sales representative.
•In the event of merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of Breaking Media’s assets, in which case personal information held by Breaking Media about its customers will be among the assets transferred to the buyer.
•Comply with any court order or other legal obligation.
•Enforce or apply our terms of use www.fashionista.com/terms-of-use and other agreements.
•Protect the rights, property, or safety of Breaking Media, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
•Cookies. If you do not wish us to collect cookies, you may set your browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you do so, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
•Promotional Offers from Third Parties. If you do not wish us to share your personal information with unaffiliated or non-agent third parties for promotional purposes, you can opt-out by checking the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your data (the order form/registration form) or by sending us an e-mail stating your request to services@breakingmedia.com.
•Promotional Offers from the Company. If you do not wish to have your e-mail address used for promotional purposes by the Company, you can opt-out by checking the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your data (the order form/registration form) or you can opt-out of the e-mail. If we have sent you a promotional e-mail, you may send us a return e-mail asking to be omitted from future e-mail distributions. This opt-out does not apply to information provided to the Company as a result of a product purchase, warranty registration, product service experience or other transactions.
•Personalized Advertising. If you do not want us to use personal information that we gather to allow third parties to personalize advertisements we display to you, you can opt-out by checking the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your data (the order form/registration form).
